[Roman Mars] This is 99% Invisible. I’m Roman Mars.
Since the early 1500s, when Sir Thomas Moore coined the term Utopia,
and probably well before then,
people have been thinking about how to design their ideal society.
Maybe it’s one that doesn’t use money.
Or one that drops the traditional family structure in favor of raising children collectively.
[Delaney Hall] One, two, check.
[Roman Mars] That’s producer Delaney Hall, getting ready to visit a sort of Utopia.
And before she left, she packed her bag,
tested her recording equipment,
grabbed a few extra packs of double A batteries and...
[Delaney Hall] I’m just gonna fill up, fill up this tub of water.
[Roman Mars] ... and then thoroughly washed every item of clothing
that she was bringing with her.
[Delaney Hall] ...have a box of baking soda.
Just dumping some of it in this tub of water. To be more specific, I soaked my clothes in a tub of baking soda for 48 hours
and showered with Doctor Bronner's unscented soap for two weeks before I left.
Got an old pair of jeans. I’m putting them in too.
[Roman Mars] Delaney reports for the show, 'State of the Reunion'.
Every episode is about a different place so she travels a lot.
But she doesn’t usually go to these kinds of extremes to get ready.
[Delaney Hall] But this is an unusual reporting trip I’m about to go on.
I’m headed to an isolated community in Eastern Arizona,
on the outskirts of a small town called Snowflake.
And the people who live there have given me very special instructions for how to get ready.
[Roman Mars] Because for some people in Snowflake,
Utopia just means not being physically sick.
A community of people who live just outside this small rural town have a medical condition called MCS,
Multiple Chemical Sensitivity.
It means they are seriously intolerant to laundry detergent, perfume,
cigarette smoke, car exhaust, commercial cleaning products.
[Delaney Hall] And Snowflake is a community designed around keeping that sort of stuff out.
People who have MCS can be seriously affected, sometimes disabled,
by migraines, muscle pains, rashes, nausea, and fatigue.
[Roman Mars] But most scientific studies have not shown a strong connection between chemical exposures and symptoms.
There’s no real medical consensus about what causes the illness.
And doctors disagree about whether symptoms are physiological,
psychological, or both.
[Delaney Hall] That means that people with MCS are often dismissed as, well,
hypochondriacs.
Many find themselves without sympathetic medical care,
or access to services that people with recognized disabilities might have.
There are a subset of doctors who believe in MCS and treat it,
but most mainstream physicians avoid the diagnosis.
And so a lot of people with the illness fall back on trial and error,
designing their diets, habits,
and environments to try and make themselves feel better.
It’s my first morning in Snowflake,
and this is really an incredible landscape. Very flat, very dry.
You can see a long way in every direction and the sky is very blue.
The houses out here are all built in a really simple style.
They look like they have sheet metal walls, pitched roofs,
they’re generally pretty small.
[Roman Mars] Delaney didn’t go to Snowflake to find out whether or not MCS was ‘real'.
She went to learn how people have built new lives and homes,
designed to fit their very particular needs out there on the remote,
grassy plateau.
[Susan Malloy] Hi, I hope you’re Delaney.
[Delaney Hall] I am, yeah.
[Susan Malloy] Hi.
[Delaney Hall] Susan Malloy has short curly hair and a wide grin.
It’s below freezing but all the windows in her small house are open.
For people with MCS,
their home is the only environment they can really control.
I’m suddenly very aware of my smell; I’m worried I didn’t prepare well enough.
Susan offers me a cup of coffee.
[Susan Malloy] Do you like milk in it?
[Delaney Hall] Sure.
[Susan Malloy] Okay.
[Delaney Hall] And then, just like I worried...
[Susan Malloy] I smell cigarettes.
[Delaney Hall] Um, what would you like me to do?
[Susan Malloy] I’m not quite sure.
[Delaney Hall] Okay.
[Susan Malloy] I’m gonna get close to you for just a sec, okay?
[Delaney Hall] Sure.
[Susan Malloy] It’s the blouse, maybe.
[Delaney Hall] Okay.
[Susan Malloy] Do you mind if I give you something else to wear?
[Delaney Hall] No, not at all.
[Susan Malloy] Okay. Well, I do have guest clothes.
[Delaney Hall] Okay.
[Roman Mars] Delaney is not a smoker, but this is the level of Susan’s sensitivity.
[Delaney Hall] Susan is at the heart of this community.
People have described her to me as a fairy god mother, and the queen.
She works with curious outsiders like me.
She also attends conferences on disability rights and spends hours each week answering phone calls from people who are sick.
She’s healthier than lots of her neighbors,
but that hasn’t always been the case.
[Susan Malloy] For me it was just real fast. I felt this,
just bizarre feeling in my head.
And my sinuses and the palette of my mouth and my throat all swelled closed.
[Delaney Hall] Susan was living in San Francisco when she first got sick,
back in the early 90’s. Her sensitivities began to cascade,
which is pretty typical for the illness.
Her allergy to chemicals grew in to a sensitivity to food and clothing,
then electricity. Telephones, computers, kitchen appliances.
Pretty much everything became toxic to her.
[Susan Malloy] Furniture had to go, the rugs had to go.
I had two girlfriends come over and take my clothes.
Just got rid of almost everything right away.
[Delaney Hall] Susan slept on friends porches, in her car, and then at her parents’.
At her sickest,
she couldn’t even drink chemically treated tap water and her mom put buckets in the yard to gather rain.
Then a friend with MCS invited her to visit Snowflake, a rural,
high altitude community with good, clean air.
He’d discovered it a few years before, driving around the country,
trying to find a place where his symptoms wouldn’t be so severe.
And when Susan visited…
[Susan Malloy] For me, the improvement was so radical. You know,
you get out of the car, you feel better. You can walk.
You don’t need the oxygen tank. Your speech is clear.
I didn’t exactly want to move here, but my body said yeah,
we’re moving here.
[Delaney Hall] For Susan, the move felt like a passage.
Like a journey between two different worlds.
[Susan Malloy] Like in the old days,
for someone to get on a ship and go to the United States from Ireland.
They didn’t really want to leave,
they just weren’t able to make it anymore and so they took this huge risk and got on a ship.
I think it felt a little like that to me.
[Roman Mars] Gradually, more people moved to Snowflake. They came from all over.
An engineer from Denmark, a marketing director from Toronto,
a chef from the Philippines, a teacher from San Francisco. Now,
there are about three dozen households scattered across this area,
all united by this illness.
[Delaney Hall] And they’re not the first people in history to move because of sickness.
[Susan Malloy] Forever,
there have's been people who’ve had to relocate because of particular medical problems or health reasons.
[Delaney Hall] In fact,
the history of medical migration to this part of the country goes back a long ways.
[Roman Mars] A hundred years ago,
doctors encouraged people with tuberculosis to head west for the same clean,
dry air that brought Susan here.
So many patients ended up in Arizona that tent cities sprouted up across the state and locals gave them a nickname: ‘lungers',
because of the hacking cough that characterized the illness.
[Susan Malloy] So this is not an uncommon experience for human beings.
Just right now’s our turn. We’re it. We’re the new guys.
[Delaney Hall] But the complicated thing about this illness is that it’s so unknown.
Some doctors would argue that this place isolates people,
pushes them deeper in to their sickness.
All the talk about diets and remedies and building techniques only reinforces what might be better treated in other ways.
But Susan told me this place saved her life.
[Susan Malloy] The kitchen’s the same as the bedroom which is the same as the living room.
I mean I basically live in one big room.
[Delaney Hall] Susan built this house herself with help from friends.
[Roman Mars] The people here in Snowflake might be the closest thing there is to a MCS think-tank.
And they’ve developed building techniques that help manage their sensitivities.
That means using ‘safe materials’,
like ceramic tiles or concrete floors instead of carpeting,
which traps chemical odors.
[Delaney Hall] Susan also used foil-lined sheet rock, which covers her walls,
giving the whole inside of her house a silver sheen.
[Susan Malloy] I just couldn’t afford to risk paint. You know,
if you get the wrong kind of paint, your whole house is unlivable.
Maybe forever,
or maybe at least for several months or a couple years.
[Delaney Hall] But maybe the most striking thing about this house is the way that Susan has isolated most of her electronics in a separate room,
which she can completely shut off from the rest of the house.
That’s because many people with MCS also experience sensitivity to electricity.
So you designed it pretty strategically with that room in mind,
the room at the front of the house is the one that….
[Susan Malloy] The only electricity comes in to one corner of the house.
It all comes in right over there and the rest of the house doesn’t have to be as affected by it.
[Delaney Hall] She keeps her television and a VCR in a separate room and she’s constructed a thick window to watch TV through,
while keeping the equipment isolated.
[Susan Malloy] The television is an ancient one, I mean by today’s standards,
and it’s really nothing special other than it's old.
I don’t want to have new chemical emissions in my house you know from plastics and so forth if there’s any way around it.
And so this one is old and aired out,
and this glass sheet in front of it is to keep the fumes in that room.
And I can open the front door and let the fumes go out without contaminating the inside of my house.
[Delaney Hall] The house is modest but you can tell how much it means to Susan.
She shows me every corner and every adaptation. It’s her safe haven.
And there are lots of people who are desperate to move out here to live in a little place just like this.
[Delaney Hall] When Susan’s phone rings, it’s usually not a good sign.
[Susan Malloy] I don’t get calls from people for whom everything is going great,
you know?
[Susan Malloy] Hello?
[Joan Robinson] Hi Susan, this is Joan Robinson. How are you?
[Susan Malloy] Hi!
[Joan Robinson] Do you know how (inaudible) is, um, available? Cause I, um,
could not being doing worse. And I’ve got to get out of here.
My skin -- I -- my skin is literally burning and bleeding from the pollution.
[Delaney Hall] Susan gets a few calls like this a week, from runners,
people who are moving from place to place,
trying to find somewhere that feels safe.
Snowflake isn’t the only community of its kind,
but it’s one of the largest and most established. Still,
that doesn’t mean there’s room for everyone.
[Susan Malloy] I’m sorry, but there is someone living there.
[Joan Robinson] Someone is living there?
[Delaney Hall] Susan tracks the limited housing in Snowflake and she breaks the bad news when she can’t help out.
[Joan Robinson] I don’t know, you never know. I’m waiting for a miracle to happen.
I need a miracle Susan, this is just incredible.
[Susan Malloy] I don’t have any miracles. I wish I did.
[Joan Robinson] I need to go. I know you’re not asking me to get off,
but I need to go cause I’m too emotional right now.
[Susan Malloy] I’m afraid that’s what a typical call is like. You know,
people who are real sick where they are and need to be in a...
another kind of housing, and there isn’t any.
[Roman Mars] Over the years,
enough people with MCS have come to Snowflake that the wider community has adapted to them.
At least a little bit.
[Delaney Hall] There’s a real estate agent who helps people find MCS friendly properties.
There’s an organic food store,
which is kind of unusual for a rural town of 5,000.
The owner there will sometimes shop for people with MCS and leave the groceries outside for them to pick up so they don’t have to come into the store,
which smells like incense. And then there’s the dentist.
[Melissa] ...and my EI patients usually come in through the back door.
They wait in their cars, and we have a separate entrance, right here.
[Roman Mars] EI is short for Environmental Illness,
another term for Multiple Chemical Sensitivity.
[Delaney Hall] Melissa is a hygienist here at Sierra Dental.
Sierra Dental regularly sees about 40 patients with MCS and they’ve adapted their practice to make it friendly to people with sensitivities.
[Melissa] And I usually tend to see them at eight o’clock in the morning,
because that’s, um,
I haven’t wiped my room down with chemicals because I did it the night before.
So I don’t have to worry about them smelling the Cavicide wipes,
which is what we use in a dental office.