[Roman Mars] This is 99% Invisible. I'm Roman Mars.
The best knock-offs in the world are in China.
Sure, designer handbags and Rolexes,
but also really large-scale imitations, like fake Apple Stores
that are so dead-on
that employees of the store think they're working in a real Apple Store.
But beyond just working in knock-offs,
many residents of Chinese suburbs live their lives in replica cities.
Venice's with complete canals and replicas of the Doge's Palace.
Paris's with Eiffel Towers and Arc de Triomphes.
There are Chrysler Buildings, Sydney Opera Houses.
[Bianca Bosker] Driving through the suburbs of any city in China,
you will find a plethora of fake Versailles, British developments,
and Californias all bumping up side-by-side.
Just Shanghai itself has ten cities all built in the architectural style of different European countries,
so it's possible to travel from Germany, to Italy,
to London in the course of a few hours,
provided there's not too much traffic.
[Roman Mars] Bianca Bosker is the author of the book Original Copies:
Architectural Mimicry in Contemporary China. And she coined a term
for these buildings: Duplitecture.
[Bianca Bosker] Duplitecture refers to this nationwide movement taking place in China,
whereby people are copying entire cities and towns from Europe
and the United States. lifesize or sometimes even bigger
than lifesize. These are not theme parks;
duplitecture developments are actually living, breathing communities
where Chinese families are raising their children,
living out their lives in a place that looks like Orange County
or Paris, but it’s smack dab in the middle of the People’s Republic.
[Roman Mars] These buildings are not just novelties, like the Pyramid
or the Eiffel Tower in Las Vegas.
[Bianca Bosker] The biggest private property developer in China told me
that two-thirds of their residential developments are being built in the European style.
[Roman Mars] Nor are they like American Chinatowns or Germantowns
which were established by immigrants. These are Chinese communities,
in American or European style buildings,
which are often designed by Chinese architects.
[Bianca Bosker] Visiting China’s copy of Paris in the outskirts of Hangzhou,
I found a place that was in some ways very emblematic of Paris.
You have the Eiffel Tower, you have the Champs-Élysées square,
but there was no new architecture.
[Roman Mars] Meaning the Chinese weren’t interested in duplicating the newer buildings of Paris,
just the old, classic looking ones that are iconic of the city.
[Bianca Bosker] At the same time, this is the most brand-new, sparkling Paris
that I’ve ever seen.
[Roman Mars] Even though these are intended to be copies,
it’s pretty much impossible to plop a building onto a completely new environment without modifying it a little,
or a lot. Oftentimes the duplitecture is larger or smaller
than the real thing. Or different elements,
or features might be bloated bigger than others.
Sometimes duplitecture gets so twisted and warped,
until it’s a freakish caricature of the original.
[Bianca Bosker] One of the interesting twists on this architectural movement has been the creation of mega-highrises,
that are built in a Baroque or a Neoclassical style.
Picture Versailles stretched 20 floors into the air,
and you’ll have some idea of what’s going on.
[Roman Mars] Developers can take a lot of liberties with duplitecture construction,
like making the replicas work in accordance with Feng Shui,
but nonetheless, a lot of these duplitecture compounds have rules
that actively discourage any type of modification
that they think might subvert the simulacrum.
[Bianca Bosker] They have very strict rules in place to ensure that Chinese elements,
or foreign elements, don’t crop in
and spoil the impression of a Paris.
And these rules have been set up to preserve the European feel of this development.
For example, no hanging laundry outside; no changing the paint;
no installing air conditioners; no keeping chickens in the back yard.
[Roman Mars] To further create the impression of Paris,
there might be a French bakery or a Bastille Day celebration.
There might be a pub in an Irish town,
or a real canal network in a knockoff Venice. As odd and uncanny
as these buildings and communities can be,
duplitecture is pretty impressive. These buildings go up quickly,
on a massive scale, and they show no signs of stopping.
Bosker saw new developments popping up around China all the time.
But duplitecture is not exactly a new trend.
[Bianca Bosker] They have a lot of practice doing this.
In premodern China you had China’s imperial rulers using copycat buildings
as a way of showing off their power and establishing their authority.
In the third century B.C.,
one of the rulers showed off his conquest of a rival kingdom by recreating their buildings within his own capital city.
[Roman Mars] You’d also have imperial hunting parks,
where rulers would import flora
and fauna of all kinds to recreate known landscapes within their own domain.
[Bianca Bosker] These imperial rulers would copy as a way of showing
that they could literally move heaven and earth.
They now possessed this foreign building or place; it was theirs.
[Roman Mars] And in keeping with that tradition,
one of the most copied buildings in China is the very seat of Western power itself.
[Bianca Bosker] The White House is generally credited
as being the most copied building in China.
And it’s used for everything from hotels to restaurants to courthouses to homes.
[Roman Mars] Just like the White House has a china collection,
China has a White House collection.
The different Chinese White Houses serve different purposes,
so they’ve morphed into various permutations.
But they all have the signature columns
and square portico built in the true blue unique style,
wholly original to the U.S. of A.
[Bianca Bosker] I hate to break it to everyone, but that’s not an original building.
The architect
who built the White House based his design on a huge building in Dublin
that is now the seat of the parliament of Ireland.
[Roman Mars] The Leinster House in Dublin,
which in turn has elements of classical Greek and Roman architecture,
and it pretty much looks like the White House even
though it’s kind of gray. It’s the gray house.
[Bianca Bosker] The founding fathers were really into duplitecture as well.
They were their own form of architectural plagiarists.
[Roman Mars] And this is so obvious if you’ve ever seen the buildings
that Thomas Jefferson designed. They were also covered in columns.
He based the Virginia state capitol on this ancient Roman temple, and
that also has gone on, in turn,
to influence the design of many many state capitols around the country.
[Bianca Bosker] Some of the greatest hits of American architecture are copies of the greatest hits of ancient Roman architecture,
which are now all being copied by the Chinese.
[Roman Mars] So we did it too. North America was ruled by Europeans,
so it makes sense
that we would have more European style architecture lying around.
But we still continue to build these European homages today.
[Bianca Bosker] When Americans build McMansions or buildings
that draw from European elements, we’re being inspired.
When the Chinese do so, they’re ripping off; they’re copying,
they’re con artists. And I think that’s unfair.
Maybe we should recognize that
what we’re all doing is copying some pretty old buildings
because we still find them attractive and we still think
that they have symbolic significance to our everyday lives.
[Roman Mars] It’s easy to scoff at knockoffs of Venice,
but these warped mimicries are the start of something new.
I say this all the time:
Stealing plus lack of talent equals creativity. What I mean there is
that in the effort to copy something, your skills or lack of skills
or different experience mutates the original so
that very often you come up with something that is completely new
and completely yours. Copying is totally underrated.
And your mindful iteration is how good things become great things.
[Bianca Bosker] China has actually proven quite successful at turning copies into innovation.
If you look at the Shen Zhai movement in China,
which is this name given for copies of the iPhone, of sneakers,
of social networks -- what you find is
that oftentimes the copies improve on the original in certain ways.
China’s iPhone knockoff, which I believe is called the Sciphone,
actually had some features you couldn’t find on Apple’s phone.
You have a removable battery, multiple SIM cards, all of these things
that Apple users really wanted and coveted.
And here you could find it in this knockoff phone.
I’m personally fascinated to see how China takes its imitation
and turns it into innovation.
[Roman Mars] 99% Invisible was produced this week by Avery Trufelman with Katie Mingle,
Sam Greenspan, and me, Roman Mars.
We are a project of 91.7 local public radio, KALW in San Francisco,
and produced by the offices of Arcsine,
a comprehensive architectural firm, in beautiful downtown Oakland, California.
Speaking of our dear East Bay,
yours truly was named best local radio host of the Best in the East Bay edition of the East Bay Express.
That totally made my day. Thanks, guys.
99% Invisible is made possible by our often imitated
but never duplicated listeners, and by TinyLetter, email
for people with something to say. My boy Maslow has something to say.
What have you got to say, Maslow?
[Maslow] Ultron is cooler than Iron Man.
[Roman Mars] Yeah, but Ultron is evil.
Yeah, and evil (...) .
[Roman Mars] TinyLetter.com is free, easy, minimal, and powerful.
It’s the simplest way to send an email newsletter.
From the great people behind Mailchimp.
This program is also made possible by the music we play during each episode.
Really, this show would be terrible without music.
The song you’re hearing right
now is 401 Circuit by Toronto’s own I Am a Robot and Proud.
This is from the Uphill City album,
but there’s also a new album called Touchtone. It’s great
and priced to move on Bandcamp. They have a link on our website.
Plus, be sure to check out all of our regular favorites. Melodium
and Set in Sand from the labels Abandoned Building and Audio Dregs,
Okay [inaudible]. Keegan DeWitt is amazing
and scores tons of our shows.
And our new friends at Ghostly International release electronic music
that we love to ruin by talking all over it.
There are too many to mention here,
but we keep lists with links on all our episode pages.
If you want to feel instantly great, today, support a musician
that you love. These guys are a good place to start.
We are a founding member of Radiotopia from PRX. It’s the all killer,
no filler radio storytelling collective.
This week on Benjamin Walker’s Theory of Everything,
if you’re looking for a good book to read this summer,
you can try to do what Phyllis Rose did.
She picked a shelf at the library, at random,
and read every book on it.
[Phyllis Rose] I am talking about reading for yourself, choosing your own reading,
and choosing it even arbitrarily,
as an extreme way of asserting your freedom.
[Roman Mars] Benjamin Walker’s Theory of Everything.
It’s just one of seven amazing shows from Radiotopia.
If you would like to sponsor 99% Invisible
or any of the shows on Radiotopia,
email sponsor@radiotopia.fm
The 99PI experience isn’t just this episode that you’re hearing,
we’re also fascinating on Twitter. You can follow us @RomanMars,
SamListens, KatieMingle, and Trufelman. We’re also on Facebook,
Tumblr, Instagram, Flickr, Soundcloud and Sonified too.
But our home on the web is 99PI.org