[Roman Mars] This is 99% Invisible. I'm Roman Mars.
Since the early 1500's, when Sir Thomas Moore coined the term Utopia,
and probably well before then, people have been thinking about
how to design their ideal society.
Maybe it's one that doesn't use money.
Or one that drops the traditional family system structure
in favor of raising children collectively.
[Delaney Hall] One, two, check.
[Roman] That's producer Delaney Hall, getting ready to visit a sort of Utopia.
And before she left, she packed her bag, tested her recording equipment,
grabbed a few extra packs of double A batteries and...
[Delaney] I'm just gonna fill up this tub of water.